Guide to the Evie C. Spencer papers, 1909-1968
Spencer, Evie C. papers, 1909-1968
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Evie C. Spencer papers, 1909-1968
37-5-2880
Evie Lee Carpenter Spencer, 1886-1984.
.3 cubic ft.
Photographs, correspondence, memorandum booklets, diplomas and certificates, Cornell ephemera, alumni surveys, and other papers.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Photographs, correspondence, memorandum booklets, diplomas and certificates, Cornell ephemera, alumni surveys, and other papers of an African-American woman student at Cornell University. Includes letters from Emily and Isabel Howland
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Evie Lee Spencer graduated from Cornell University in 1918.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Photographs, correspondence, memorandum booklets, diplomas and certificates, Cornell ephemera, alumni surveys, and other papers of an African-American woman student at Cornell University. Includes letters from Emily and Isabel Howland
SUBJECTS
Names:
Spencer, Evie Lee Carpenter, 1886-1984.; Howland, Emily, 1827-1929.; Howland, Isabel, 1959-1942.; Cornell University--Students.
Subjects:
Women college students--New York (State)--Ithaca.; African American college students--New York (State)--Ithaca.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Biographical Information, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1913, 1918, 1922, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1933, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1935, 1938, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1951, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Copies of Howland-Spencer Correspondence, 1913-1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Fiftieth Reunion, 1918, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Women (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Photographs, 1913-1951 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Cornell Paperweight (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Three Address Cards (Box 1, Folder 13)
- "Flower Guide" (Box 1, Folder 14)
- "Land Bird's Bird Guide" (Box 1, Folder 15)
- "I Have Called You Friends" (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Confederate Five Dollar bill and coin (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Diary, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Diary, 1914-1936 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Memo Book, pre-1922, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Address Book, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Diary, 1922-1924 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Memo Book, 1935-1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Address Book, 1940's (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Memo Book, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Memo Book, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Memo Book, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Memo Book, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Memo Book, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Address Book, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Memo Book, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Doodle Diary, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Memo Book/Diary, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Memo Book, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Memo Book, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Address Book, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 19)